<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<extradoc>
		<class name="HSL">
				<summary>
						This class is not an abstract class, but used as one for each internal color class.
						This is so it can be used internally with an extension "Chizl.ColorExtensions.Info".
						Info() to be used on Microsoft's Color struct and ConsoleColor enum.<br/>
						<b>Understand Hue w/ Quotes from:</b> <a href="https://color-wheel-artist.com/hue/">color-wheel-artist.com</a><br/>
						Tint is sometimes also called a Pastel, but to be precise, Color Theory defines a True Tint as any Hue or mixture of pure colors with only White added.<br/>
						Color Theory defines a True Tone as any Hue or mixture of pure colors with only Gray added. To be precise, this definition considers Gray as truly neutral.<br/>
						Color Theory defines a True Shade​ as any pure Hue or mixture of pure colors with only Black added. In other words, it contains absolutely no White or Gray.<br/>
						<b>(4) Depths in a Color Wheel:</b><br/>
						<li>4. Hue - Most Outside, Pure Color</li><br/>
						<li>3. Tints - Hue + White</li><br/>
						<li>2. Tones - Hew + Gray</li><br/>
						<li>1. Shade - Most Inner, Hue + Black</li>
				</summary>
				<returns></returns>
				<interfaces>
						<interface name="HSLInt">
								<summary>
										HSV(int decValue) or HSB(int decValue):<br/>
										RGB decimal value from or to create Color.<br/>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
						<interface name="HSLColor">
								<summary>
										HSV(System.Drawing.Color) or HSB(System.Drawing.Color):<br/>
										Color object to build RGB decimal value from or to create Color.<br/>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
				</interfaces>
				<properties>
						<property name="HSL_Saturation">
								<summary>
										Definition: The degree of colorfulness relative to the lightness of the color.<br/>
										Represents: How intense or muted a hue is, based on how much gray is mixed in at a given lightness level.<br/>
										Range: 0.00% (completely desaturated, gray) to 100.00% (fully saturated, pure hue).<br/>
										Behavior:<br/>
										- Low Saturation: The color appears muted, soft, or closer to gray.<br/>
										- High Saturation: The color is vivid and intense.<br/>
										Interpretation: At 0% saturation, the result is a shade of gray (regardless of the hue).
										At 100%, the color is as pure as possible at that lightness level.
										HSL saturation varies nonlinearly with lightness — very light or very dark colors naturally appear less saturated even at 100%.<br/>
										Note: Unlike HSV, which measures saturation relative to value (brightness), HSL saturation is
										calculated relative to lightness, which is the average of the maximum and minimum RGB components.
										This makes HSL more perceptually intuitive for generating tints, shades, and tones.
								</summary>
								<returns>
										(double)<br/>
										- Min Value: 0.00<br/>
										- Max Value: 100.00<br/>
								</returns>
						</property>
						<property name="HSL_Lightness">
								<summary>
										Definition: The perceived light/dark level of a color in the HSL model.<br/>
										Representation: Midpoint between black and white, where 0% is black, 50% is the pure color, and 100% is white.<br/>
										Range: 0.00% (black) to 100.00% (white).<br/>
										Interpretation:<br/>
										- Low Lightness: The color is closer to black and appears dark or shadowy.<br/>
										- Mid Lightness (≈50%): Pure hue without added black or white.<br/>
										- High Lightness: The color is closer to white and may appear pastel or washed out.<br/>
										Note: Unlike HSV, HSL lightness mixes both white and black, producing a symmetrical scale around the pure hue.
								</summary>
								<returns>
										(double)<br/>
										- Min Value: 0.00<br/>
										- Max Value: 100.00<br/>
								</returns>
						</property>
				</properties>
		</class>
</extradoc>