<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<extradoc>
		<class name="HSVB">
				<summary>
						The HSV (Hue, Saturation, Value) aka HSB (Hue, Saturation, Brightness)<br/>
						HSV is also sometimes referred to as HSB, where B stands for Brightness instead of Value, but the meaning and value is the same.<br/><br/>
						This color model is a way of representing colors that is more intuitive for human perception than the RGB (Red, Green, Blue) model.<br/>
						HSV divides color into three components:<br/>
						Hue, which represents the color's base, like red, green, or blue.  The value represented the angle or degree on a RGB color wheel, ranging from 0.00 to 360.00 degrees.<br/>
						Saturation, which indicates the of purity or intensity percentage (%) of the color.  A fully saturated color will be a pure, vibrant shade, while a lower saturation will make the color appear muted or grayscale.<br/>
						Value aka Brightness, represents the brightness percentage (%) of the color, ranging from black(0%) to white(100%).<br/>
						HSV is often represented as a cylinder or cone, with:<br/>
						- Hue: around the circular base,<br/>
						- Saturation: as radius from center to edge,<br/>
						- Value/Brightness, as height from bottom (black) to top (brightest color).<br/>
				</summary>
				<returns></returns>
				<interfaces>
						<interface name="HSVBInt">
								<summary>
										HSV(int decValue) or HSB(int decValue):<br/>
										RGB decimal value from or to create Color.<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
						<interface name="HSVBColor">
								<summary>
										HSV(System.Drawing.Color) or HSB(System.Drawing.Color):<br/>
										Color object to build RGB decimal value from or to create Color.<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
						<interface name="HSVBDoubles">
								<summary>
										HSV(double hue, double saturation, double value) or HSB(double hue, double saturation, double value):<br/>
										Hue, Saturation, and Value/Brightness values for Color object.<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
				</interfaces>
				<properties>
						<property name="HSVB_Saturation">
								<summary>
										Definition: The purity or intensity percentage (%) of the color.<br/>
										Represents: How much the color deviates from a neutral gray at the same brightness.<br/>
										Range: 0.00% (completely unsaturated, gray) to 100.00% (fully saturated, pure hue).<br/>
										Behavior:<br/>
										- Low Saturation: Colors appear grayish, pastel, or washed out.<br/>
										- High Saturation: Colors are vivid, rich, and intense.<br/>
										Interpretation: Saturation in HSV indicates how "pure" the hue is.
										A saturation of 0% means there's no colorfulness (the result is a shade of gray).
										As saturation increases, the hue becomes more prominent.<br/>
										Note: HSV and HSL define saturation differently. In HSV, saturation is based on the distance
										from the center of the HSV cylinder, whereas in HSL it’s based on chroma relative to lightness.
								</summary>
								<returns>
										(double)<br/>
										- Min Value: 0.00<br/>
										- Max Value: 100.00<br/>
								</returns>
						</property>
						<property name="HSVB_Value">
								<summary>
										Definition: The brightness or luminosity of a color.<br/>
										Representation: Represents how much light is present in a color, from dark (black) to fully lit (pure color).<br/>
										Range: 0.00% (black) to 100.00% (full brightness).<br/>
										Interpretation:<br/>
										- Low Value: The color appears darker or shadowed.<br/>
										- High Value: The color appears brighter and more intense.<br/>
										Note: Affects how "light" or "dark" a color appears but does not consider white—only black is mixed in at low values.<br/>
										Also Note: HSV aka HSB, where B stands for Brightness instead of Value, but the meaning and value is the same.
								</summary>
								<returns>
										(double)<br/>
										- Min Value: 0.00<br/>
										- Max Value: 100.00<br/>
								</returns>
						</property>
						<property name="HSVB_RawValue">
								<summary>
										Definition: The brightness or luminosity of a color in the HSV model.<br/>
										Representation: Represents how much light is present in a color, from dark (black) to fully lit (pure color).<br/>
										Range: 0.00% (black) to 100.00% (full brightness).<br/>
										Interpretation:<br/>
										- Low Value: The color appears darker or shadowed.<br/>
										- High Value: The color appears brighter and more intense.<br/>
										Note: Affects how "light" or "dark" a color appears but does not consider white—only black is mixed in at low values.<br/>
										Also Note: HSV is also sometimes referred to as HSB, where B stands for Brightness instead of Value, but the meaning and value is the exact same.
								</summary>
								<returns>
										(double)<br/>
										- Min Value: 0.00<br/>
										- Max Value: 100.00<br/>
								</returns>
						</property>
				
		</properties>
		</class>
</extradoc>