<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<extradoc>
		<class name="LAB">
				<summary>
						LAB and LUV (L*, a*, b*, u*, v*): These color spaces are derived from the XYZ space and are designed to be perceptually uniform, 
						meaning that the numerical distance between colors in these spaces corresponds more closely to the perceived difference in color 
						by the human eye than in the XYZ space.<br/>
						<br/>
						The L* value represents lightness, typically ranging from 0 to 100, where 0 is black and 100 is white.<br/>
						The a* (red-green) and b* (blue-yellow) values in CIELAB,<br/>
						<br/>
						A negative value indicates a shift towards blue.<br/>
						A small negative value here means a very subtle blue tint.<br/>
						The combination of these small negative 'a' and 'b' values suggests a color that is very close to neutral gray, but with a slight leaning towards the blue-green side, which is characteristic of a pale azure.<br/>
						The LAB color space is designed to be perceptually uniform, meaning that numerical differences in the values correspond to similar perceived color differences by humans.<br/>
						<br/>
						These values indicate the position along the color axes, with negative values indicating one direction (e.g., green or blue) and positive values indicating the other (e.g., red or yellow).<br/>
						They can exceed the typical -100 to 100 range for highly saturated colors. These values are essentially coordinates within a defined color space, and they don't inherently require a unit like percentages or degrees.
				</summary>
				<returns></returns>
				<interfaces>
						<interface name="LABInt">
								<summary>
										RGB decimal value from Color.<br/>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
						<interface name="LABColor">
								<summary>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
				</interfaces>
				<properties>
						<property name="L">
								<summary>
										L (Lightness):<br/>
										- Similar to LCH, this confirms the color is very light. The 'L' component in LAB ranges from 0 (black) to 100 (white).<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
						<property name="A">
								<summary>
										A (Green–Red axis)<br/>
										- The 'A' component represents the green-red axis.<br/>
										- Negative values indicates a shift towards green. In this case, a small negative value means a very subtle green tint.<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
						<property name="B">
								<summary>
										B (Blue–Yellow axis)<br/>
										- The 'B' component represents the blue-yellow axis.<br/>
										- Negative values indicates a shift towards blue. A small negative value here means a very subtle blue tint. <br/>
										- The combination of these small negative 'a' and 'b' values suggests a color that is very close to neutral gray, but with a slight leaning towards the blue-green side, which is characteristic of a pale azure.<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
				</properties>
		</class>
</extradoc>