<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<extradoc>
		<class name="LUV">
				<summary>
						LUV is derived from the CIE 1931 XYZ color space through specific mathematical transformations.<br/>
						LUV represents color using three components: L* (lightness), u* (chromaticity), and v* (chromaticity).<br/>
						The L* value represents lightness, typically ranging from 0 to 100, where 0 is black and 100 is white.<br/>
						The u* and v* components represent chromaticity, with u* indicating a red-green axis and v* indicating a blue-yellow axis.<br/>
						<br/>
						LAB and LUV (L*, a*, b*, u*, v*): These color spaces are derived from the XYZ space and are designed to be perceptually uniform,<br/>
						meaning that the numerical distance between colors in these spaces corresponds more closely to the perceived difference in color<br/>
						by the human eye than in the XYZ space.<br/>
						<br/>
						The L* value represents lightness, typically ranging from 0 to 100, where 0 is black and 100 is white.<br/>
						The u* (green-red) and v* (blue-yellow) values in CIELUV represent chromaticity coordinates.<br/>
						<br/>
						These values indicate the position along the color axes, with negative values indicating one direction (e.g., green or blue) and positive values
						indicating the other (e.g., red or yellow).<br/>
						They can exceed the typical -100 to 100 range for highly saturated colors.  These values are essentially coordinates within a defined color space, and they don't inherently require a unit like percentages or degrees.<br/>
				</summary>
				<returns></returns>
				<interfaces>
						<interface name="LUVInt">
								<summary>
										RGB decimal value from Color.<br/>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
						<interface name="LUVColor">
								<summary>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
				</interfaces>
				<properties>
						<property name="L">
								<summary>
										L* (Lightness): Represents the perceived brightness or lightness of a color, ranging from 0 (black) to 100 (white).<br/>
										This component is identical to the L* component in the CIELAB color space.<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
						<property name="U">
								<summary>
										u* (Red-Green Chromaticity): Represents the color’s position on a red-green axis, where positive values indicate a shift towards red and negative values indicate a shift towards green.										
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
						<property name="V">
								<summary>
										v* (Blue-Yellow Chromaticity): Represents the color’s position on a blue-yellow axis, where positive values indicate a shift towards yellow and negative values indicate a shift towards blue.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
				</properties>
		</class>
</extradoc>