<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<extradoc>
		<class name="XYZ">
				<summary>
						The CIE XYZ color space is one of the earliest mathematical representation of all colors visible to the human eye, serving as a standard reference for other color spaces.<br/>
						It's defined by three imaginary primary colors (X, Y, and Z), where Y represents luminance (brightness), and X and Z represent chromaticity (color).<br/>
						This space is device-independent, meaning it can be used to describe colors without being tied to a specific display or printing technology.<br/>
						The XYZ color space serves as a fundamental reference for many other color spaces, but distances in this space do not directly reflect perceived color differences as accurately as LAB or LUV.<br/>
						The XYZ color space is often used as a reference to convert from one color space to another, making it a crucial tool in color management.
				</summary>
				<returns></returns>
				<interfaces>
						<interface name="XYZInt">
								<summary>
										RGB decimal value from or to create Color.<br/>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
						<interface name="XYZColor">
								<summary>
										Color object to build RGB decimal value from or to create Color.<br/>
										If alpha or transparency is included it will be ignored.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</interface>
				</interfaces>
				<methods>
						<method name="AdaptXyz">
								<summary>
										Performs chromatic adaptation on an XYZ color from a source illuminant to a destination illuminant using the Bradford (von Kries) method.<br/>
										<paramref name="xyz"/> - The source XYZ color.<br/>
										<paramref name="sourceWhite"/> - The source illuminant (e.g., Common.D65).<br/>
										<paramref name="destWhite"/> - The destination illuminant (e.g., Common.D50).<br/>
								</summary>
								<returns>A new XyzSpace color adapted to the new illuminant.</returns>
						</method>
				</methods>
				<properties>
						<property name="X">
								<summary>
										'X' and 'Z' represent chromaticity (color).
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
						<property name="Y">
								<summary>
										'Y' specifically represents the luminance or perceived brightness of the color.<br/>
										Using example color Azure (#F0FFFF), "XYZ [90, 97, 109]", 'Y' value of 97 confirms that Azure is a very bright color and consistent with its high lightness values in LCH and LAB.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
						<property name="Z">
								<summary>
										Higher 'Z' values (which are more sensitive to blue light) and higher 'Y' values (for brightness) relative to 'X' values are characteristic of light blue colors.
								</summary>
								<returns></returns>
						</property>
				</properties>
		</class>
</extradoc>